Yagmur!
Yagmur, stop!
Water and Fire
''There is no such thing
as coincidence.
lf it's meant to happen,
it happens.
All of this was meant to happen,
and it did.
Fire met water.
But neitherthe waterevaporated,
northe fire went out.
The flames
swallowed the entire city.
All they felt was pain.
And what a pain...''
Honey,
l loved the book's cover.
l'm so excited!
You are the first
to officially read the book.
Call me when you finish it.
l know.
l promise, l'll finish it by evening,
l'll call you then.
l love you, honey.
l love you too.
''Theirfirst time meeting
had been painful.
The man was already scarred but
did not show it.
The beads of sweat on his face were
the only sign of the pain inside.''
-Are you okay, brother?.
-l'm fine, l'm fine.
-lf you need anything, let me know.
-Alright.
God damn it.
How many times do l have to say
that l don't want a window seat?
l'm so sorry.
Sorry. Excuse me...
l have a fear of flying,
l wasn't even aware. Well...
Let me see that.
l clawed you very badly,
l'm so sorry.
This is why l don't like to fly.
l know that the fearis unfounded,
but l'm still scared.
l'm so sorry.
Brother, this is a safe place.
Necmi's place is very close to here.
You didn't do anything wrong,
brother.
You didn't run.
You did the right thing.
You are not to blame
in what has happened.
These places are yours,
you've probably missed it.
Do not leave my side, okay?
Go on.
Help with the luggage, come on.
-Alright, brother.
Hasmet!
l'm starving,
when will you be done?
-l'll be down in half an hour.
-Alright.
Hey, Nick!
There's no problem, sir,
and we are at Necmi's place now.
How's he doing?
Good.
Don't let him do anything crazy,
like coming back here.
You are in control there, Turhan.
l'm going to be gone for a while.
The issue has gone to the police
in a different light. Not good.
Alright, sir. Don't worry,
everything is fine here.
Okay then.
Hasmet, it's good
that you've been sent here.
Kemal Aslan. Tarik Aslan.
Please make do with these for now,
in any case.
The Turks here
don't know who you are.
lf you happen to need anything,
call me.
You are young men.
Do you understand?
-Brother?. Are you okay?
-l'm fine, l'm fine.
Let me see that wound.
lt's infected.
Don't you ever get bandaged up?
-l did it myself in the moming.
-Alpago?
-Yes, sir.
-Give me a pencil and paper.
-Of course, sir.
Now, you are going to the address
written here. lt's our hospital.
There won't be anything to do
with the police.
They should bandage it up properly.
What do you have on your hand?
Okay, dad, okay.
Look, take your medication.
You soak yourself from top to
bottom while gardening, that's why.
Alright.
Okay, spoiled daddy.
Okay, kisses,
don't worry about me, okay?
Bye.
-Why are you laughing?
-No reason. What are you eating?
Didn't you bring this?
lt was on the counter.
l spread it on some bread.
-Spit it out!
Spit it out, girl,
there are walnuts in it!
-What?
-Spit it out!
Who's supposed to be
taking care of who?
l brought you all the way here.
l'm tired.
You take me a little ways, honey.
You should have written
that it had walnuts in it, on it.
lf you hadn't jumped on it
so fast,...
...l suppose l would have had
the time to write on it.
l'm all itchy.
Who is that?
l swear, it's a coincidence.
You were walking though.
My friend is allergic to walnuts and
got poisoned.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
-l came for bandages.
-Did l claw you that bad?
-Yeah, l almost died.
-l'm so sorry.
-Just kidding.
l had a little accident,
that's all...
Do you live here?
''This was a question
without an answer.
The only thing he knew was
that to live, he had to be here.
But instead of answering,...
...the man preferred to let himself
be intoxicated by hersweet voice.''
l neverknew that this pain,
Would cause you to stray,
And rob me of my heart.
Look, she composed this song herself.
Very nice, isn't it?
l don't know much about this kind of
music, but it sounds good.
Do you work with music as well?
No.
l came here to study English.
Tourism is a good job
where l'm from.
But everything changed
when l met lrem.
My school is over, but l decided to
stay fora while longer.
My fatherwas
a little hard to convince,...
...but that's a separate topic.
She was very helpful.
Even found me a job.
By the way,
l'm a hairdresser.
Ourshop is up ahead,
not too far away.
Now, you tell me.
-What should l tell?
Who is Kemal?
l don't know.
We've only just met as well.
You ran away from something
and have come to collect yourself.
l get it.
How long will you be here,
the wise man who sold his Ferrari?
-Along time.
-How long?
For example, three months,
a few weeks, a single day?
You never know, fate is fate.
Good, good.
Let him relax a little bit.
Yes, sir.
-Yourbrothers?
-That handsome one is my brother.
Different mothers, same father.
My mother passed away.
His motherraised me, Lady Fadile.
Lady Fadile is a good person,
l consider herto be my mother.
Alpago is like my brother,
his father left him to us.
l lost my motheras well.
But it has been a long time.
l can vaguely remember herface.
She was a tough woman.
My dad is like a flower.
But, my mom, you know...
l wish l she were here.
What happened?
Don't look at me like that,...
...l can't look at anyone in the eyes
fortoo long.
This orthis?
The guy will stuff lahmacun
in yourmouth.
You are going to come home
with yourmouth buming.
So this shoe, orthis shoe?
Put on yourboots and go.
How dare you talk about my lord
that way?
What are you laughing at?
Oh, nevermind.
You have come
to do big things here now, huh?
What big things? For example,
construction orsomething?
Sort of.
lt is what it is. Welcome.
lt is good that you've come.
Look, you are laughing again.
Come on, tell me what's so funny,
so that l can laugh too.
l'm laughing at lrem.
She thought you would take me
to eat lahmacun.
lf she were to see this...
We are not at the level of
eating lahmacun yet.
lf we were eating lahmacun, it would
mean that it's over and done.
What's overand done?
Look, l'm not so great
at this romantic stuff.
Don't push it.
You are such a different man.
You are always walking around
with a posse. You neversmile.
You are like a big sirtype,
but at the moment, in front of me...
...you are an embarrassed kid,
a five year old child.
Look, not smiling still.
l want to see yourteeth.
Show me.
-Wait, it hurts... Stop, it hurts.
-Show me yourteeth.
-Stop, don't, how shameful!
-What's shameful, show me yourteeth.
He wants to move faraway,
out of the city.
l don't know,
it hasn't been even been a year.
What should l do?
Your eyes are like bottomless pits.
l'm afraid of falling,
but they are drawing me in.
With you, it's always the extremes.
lt's eitherheaven orhell.
Who are you, Kemal?
l'm a speck of dust.
One winds tossed,
carried to the clouds.
Mixed with rains,
falling onto unknown lands.
The prisoner of fate.
l'm a speck of dust.
Ready for everything.
Have you everbeen in love?
Not enough to create poetry
while looking into a person's eyes.
-Did you create this just now?
-Don't you like it?
So, what about you?
-What?
-Have you ever been in love?
Stop.
Don't look at me like that.
l can't look at anyone in the eyes
fortoo long.
Stop! Stop!
''The man was in pain.
lt was not because of his wound,
it was the pain of having killed.
The girl touched his wounds.
She didn't care about the reasons.
She only cared about one thing.''
Does it hurt a lot?
Can l get you some water?.
Do you want anything?
Hold on.
''Yagmur became the medicine
for Hasmet's wounds,...
...it was the beginning of change.
He was falling in love.
Not just because she was
very beautiful, which she was.
Hasmet was either changing,
orbecoming himself again.
To love Yagmurwas...
...to keep away from everything
he had lived through.
lt was a great opportunity
to know himself again.
He loved her.''
''Winter doesn't only tum
a city cold,...
...but some of the hearts
in it as well.''
What happened?
l bumed my finger in the pan,
it hurts, it hurts a lot.
What are you doing?
That feels so good.
-The eggs are very good.
-Enjoy your meal.
Stop eating that, you are nasty,
l put my finger in it.
What's nasty?
Tastes like Kanlica yogurt.
Kemal. l miss Turkey.
When do we go there?
Also, l can't keep hiding you
from my fatheranymore.
So, tell him.
No, not like this.
l can't say it overthe phone.
lf l go there now, l can break
the news about you gently.
Then you can meet,
then perhaps...
First, get my motherto like you,
the rest is easy.
-Won't she like me?
-No, she is slow to like people.
lf she wasn't,
would l be single now?
How many girls have you introduced
to herso far?.
You are an ass!
l miss you so much.
l am going to come.
l am going to come,
but my fearof flying...
Okay, dad, kisses, bye.
Kemal, aren't we going to go out
fordinner?.
You are making me eat
this disgusting thing.
Wait, let me show them
how it's done.
Are you alright, baby?
You feed me this disgusting thing,
then you ask me if l'm alright.
l can't tell him, mom.
Let brother Hamza come
and tell him himself.
He won't listen to me.
He will listen to him.
Okay, l'm sending Hamza.
Son, you take care of yourself
out there.
Come on, man, come on.
Come on, let's go.
Are you sure?
Take a few more tests.
l finished ten boxes,
it's all positive.
You fell in love and got pregnant.
My dear...
Wait, why are you crying?
Listen to me.
Okay, okay, l got emotional.
We met a yearago, today.
l bought him a gift.
l will tell him when l present it.
Girl, you are giving him
the best gift there is.
l hope he cherishes it.
Oh, Tarik is there.
Let's talk later, lrem, okay?
Kisses.
Welcome, Tarik.
-Thank you, Yagmur.
l got you everything that you wanted.
-Thank you.
l was talking to lrem just now...
l've missed her.
Did you hear it?
l heard, Yagmur.
Tarik, what will happen?
Please tell me.
Are we going to Turkey?
What do we do?
l can't tell my dad about this.
Yagmur...
Mr. Hamza has arrived,...
...they are with my brother
at Necmi's place now. Talking.
My brother might go to lstanbul.
Have the problems
been taken care of?
Look, Yagmur,
don't ask me anything now.
Don't say anything to my brother
until he retums.
lt will be betterto speak
when my brother has retumed.
Trust me.
-But...
-Yagmur... Trust me.
They know of yourplace here.
Sitki has been following you
fora few months.
Now, they are also aware.
The only thing we need
to end this conflict...
...is for both sides
to show the white flag.
We are on the verge of bankruptcy,
Hasmet. They are as well.
Mr. Resit said, ''if Hasmet retums,
we will find a peaceful way''.
What is this ''peaceful way'', Hamza?
Are they trying to draw us out
into the open?
No, they are not, trust me.
Neitherside has the means
to keep this fight going.
Brother Necmi, what do you think?
Yesterday,
l spoke with Lady Fadile.
She said, ''if Hasmet retums,
it will resolve this mess''.
My opinion is that you go. Besides,
my guys will be there beside you.
l know Resit,
he's not like his older brother.
The guy is sick anyways.
Obviously, he's trying to
make things right before he goes.
''She's Pregnant''
l'm fine, l'm fine.
Hamza, Yagmur is asking,
will you stay overtonight?
-No, no. l shouldn't.
-Stay.
No, l'm going to go
and clean up around the place.
Good.
He won't, baby.
l have some good news.
We will talk this evening.
The captivity ends, huh?
Can we leave the girl out of this,
Hasmet?
-''The girl''?
-l mean Yagmur.
Ourdestination is certain,
the center of the fire.
lt's not clearwhat will happen.
She doesn't know the customs,
orthe people...
What is she going to do there?
-l know what to do, Hamza.
No one knows how to mess things up
betterthan him.
He says he knows what to do.
He should,
since he screwed everything up.
How can he speak to me like that?
What are you mumbling about, Hamza?
Aunt, l'm retuming.
How was it?
l swearto God, l don't know
if it went good orif it went bad.
This girl will be a nuisance.
Hamza, that issue will be handled.
Aunt, she's pregnant.
Can you hearme, aunt?
Hamza,
l will not repeat what l said.
Aunt, l...
She's pregnant, what can l do?
Do l need to tell you what to do?
Do whatever is necessary.
We had met on this day, last year.
l hurt this hand.
This is an apology addressed
from this hand, to this one.
But this is not a simple watch.
lt's very nice.
We are leaving.
Don't scream, stop.
Are you serious?
Things worked out, but first,
l have to go to Turkey alone.
Look, when l retum,
everything will have changed.
What if you don't retum?
Take me with you, please.
l will go crazy here without you.
Don't worry, Tarik will be here.
He will not leave you alone.
l have to go.
When l come back,
l will have solved everything.
Then, we will go together.
You are coming back, aren't you?
Will you be my wife?
Yes.
When you get back,
l will have a surprise for you.
-Welcome, Mr. Hasmet.
-Hello.
-Brother, welcome.
-My dearsister!
Did you miss me?
-How can l not miss my brother?
-Ask me about it. Where is mom?
-lnside, waiting for you.
Come on.
l'm your mothertoo.
My heart hurts for you
when something happens,...
...just as if it had happened
to Turhan.
Only God knows what l had to
endure here forthe past year.
There is no otherway.
This is your responsibility.
Only you can handle this situation.
l don't have it in me,
nor does this family...
...to lift anotherfuneral
from this house.
Hasmet, they know
where you are staying there.
lf you care about this family...
...and what your late father
entrusted to you,...
...you will do it.
Where is Hamza?
At ourhometown. From there,
he is organizing the attendees.
He will be here
on the day of the meeting.
-Yagmur?
-Tarik.
-Tarik, where are we?
-lt's a surprise, Yagmur. Asurprise.
-lt's Kemal.
-Yagmur, give me the phone.
Look, you are going to mess up
the whole surprise. Come on.
Hamza?
Tarik, what's going on?
Sit down.
Do you know
who it is that you are with?
What does that mean, Hamza?
lt means,
the fairy tale is over now.
Now come the facts.
His name is Hasmet.
Hasmet Ayaz.
Before he came here,...
...he killed the head of one of
Turkey's most dangerous families.
He killed Mr. lhsan.
That is why
he has been here for a year.
What did he tell you
about his wounds?
This is the shootout
where he was injured.
They wanted to get things done
themselves.
That's why, this issue was reflected
differently to the police.
Both families
have had many funerals.
Finally, through my efforts,
we came to an agreement.
lf this agreement goes through,...
...it ends the rage that's been
going on formany years.
Both families will be able to avoid
bankruptcy.
Here's the only one obstacle
in theirway:
You.
Who, me?
To get rid of you, both families
will do everything they can.
They know
where Hasmet is hiding here.
They know about you as well.
There is no othersolution,
you must leave Hasmet.
l don't believe you,
let him tell me himself.
When he retums,
he will tell you the same.
What l'm saying is,
no matterwhat he tells you,...
...you shouldn't go back to Turkey
with him.
-l'm pregnant.
-Yes, we know.
lt would be much easier
if you weren't,...
...but we will take care of that,
don't worry.
What do you mean,
you will take care of it?
Let's get you off to this side,
the doctorwill take care of it.
Let go, let go!
What are you doing? Let go!
What are you doing?
Tarik! Tarik, help me, please!
-Brother Hamza!
-l don't think you understand me!
l said there is a blood feud,
Hasmet will die.
This is not a joke.
l don't make jokes.
Now, get rid of that bastard
and go away, or l will kill you!
Brother...
l'm going to the airport.
When this is done, take herback
to where you picked her up.
Explain to herwhat she should do
very carefully.
What we are doing is wrong.
So, all what's been done to date
is alright, but this is wrong.
Come on, Turhan, come on,
do as you are told.
This is illegal.
Yagmur!
From the day l lost my brother,
a part of me has been gone as well.
Another death...
...will disturb me in my grave.
Turhan is young.
Sitki...
You...
Hamza...
lt would be a pity.
Some of you are in the soil,
a bunch of you are in prison.
The young
will control theirtempers.
There is a blessing in a wedding.
This so-called peace
should not just be said in words.
Through marriage,
the blood feud will stop.
Marry ourdaughter, Nupelda.
Then, we will become relatives.
The hundreds of members of
this family will only allow as such.
Nupe, she grew up
on the same streets as you.
She knows you.
We asked her.
We received her approval.
lt was voluntary.
Let this rage end.
Provide us with grandkids.
Nothing else will douse this fire.
Now, if there is anyone against this
marriage, let them leave here now.
l don't need your permission!
What's this supposed to mean?
l'll nevertrust you, Hasmet!
Hasmet!
Be wise!
Everybody should be wise.
''Hasmet was the man she loved
since childhood.
The woman thought:
'Who am l looking at?'
Was it herhusband,...
...or herfather's killer?''
What are you doing?
You are trying to add fuel to a fire
we are trying to put out.
All of the efforts we had to put in
just to get it to this point...
What do you want,
Turhan to be killed?
Should they just shoot you again?
Do you want to lose everything
yourfatherleft behind?
Tell them to wait for my answer.
You don't need to go.
l told Turhan,
he told Yagmureverything.
Hamza... Hamza...
Hamza, what did you do?
She's looking at us.
l heard she escaped,
why didn't you tell me?
Calm down, listen.
''Calm down''?
What do you mean, ''calm down''?
She fled,
but had an accident while fleeing.
Kemal...
She had a miscarriage.
That's God work for you. You see?
He didn't will it either.
You are sure, right?
The doctor just left.
The girl is miserable.
She had a miscarriage.
Hamza, food is ready.
Good.
Look, Hasmet is on his way there.
Now, the rest is up to you.
That girl will not come here.
Alright.
Why?
They want him to marry
the daughterof the man he killed.
My brotherhas to do it.
This blood feud is to be eliminated
through a wedding.
The situation is very serious.
You have to go.
lf you won't think about yourself,
think about my brother.
This is no joke,
they will kill him.
lf my brothercomes here,
sees you,...
...he won't let go
when he finds out about the baby.
He will endanger
both his life and yours.
Yagmur, if you love my brother,
stay away from him.
He proposed to me.
There is no otherchoice, Yagmur.
lf you love my brother, leave.
Go, Yagmur.
lf you love my brother.
Yagmur!
Where is she?
-She's gone.
Where did she go?
Hamza said to tell her,
so l told her.
She took her belongings and took off.
l couldn't stop her.
What do you mean
you couldn't stop her?
Hamza told me that you knew,
and so l told her.
What should l have done?
Why do you have her phone?
She forgot it on herway out,
on the table.
Get out of here!
''That powerful man was crying
in the middle of the city.
The burdens
that he thought he had left behind...
...were, again,
riding on his shoulders,...
...more severe and more cruel
this time.''
l nevertrusted that man
in the first place.
Yagmur, my baby...
No way,
no way will he everfind you again.
God damn him.
Don't curse him.
He doesn't even know about it.
-Look at you...
-lrem, what do l do now?
ls this the point
they have brought you to?
Were you like this before?
Let him go on looking for you.
Kemal is such a jerk!
What, so his name was Hasmet...
The man is a complete fraud.
What happened?
What's going on?
lrem, is he here?
Hello, lrem. Yagmurand l
have been going through some things.
l can't find her.
l thought she would be here.
Look, it wasn't my fault.
There's something l need to tell her.
lf she's here,
let me just talk to her.
Come with me.
Look, Kemal,
orwhoever you are.
She's a strangerto yourworld.
She sees these things only
from watching TVand movies.
l think you should
stop chasing her.
Leave the girl and us alone.
-Yagmur?
-Kemal, stop.
-Let go.
-Kemal, l said ''stop''.
-Let me go, lrem.
-Kemal, no.
-Hey!
-Yagmur! lrem, get off me!
-l said ''no''!
Yagmur!
Kemal...
Kemal!
You know, he was deported,
he can't go back.
But he may ask you to help.
Necmi.
Keep that girl away from Hasmet.
Don't worry, Lady Fadile, l am aware
of the seriousness of the situation.
He called me already,
l'll handle it.
You saw them there.
A blonde, huh?
Was she pretty?
Pathetic, compared to you.
Ah, Nupe...
You think l would have been that
quiet if you weren't there, huh?
l would have killed all of them.
That man shot my father,
he died in my arms.
Now, l call ourfather's killer
my brother-in-law, huh?
Anyways, l won't say anything.
But just so you know this, sister,
l will always be alert.
l won't accept it. l can't.
Not a sound from you, Sitki.
You won't make a single sound
until l tell you.
You will bear it until l say so.
Of course l'm sorry
forwhat has happened.
As l said, l found the girl.
l was kicked out.
Unspeakable remarks were made.
You know that other girl,
the girl that's with her...
They relocated to Canada.
Never mind now, nevermind.
Look, things are working out
overthere.
Don't go raising this topic.
Okay, Necmi, okay.
Thank you.
Hush.
Hush, don't bark.
Our girl has come.
Ourgirl...
My daughter, Yagmur.
When did you get here?
Why didn't you let me know?
Since when
have you been sitting there?
Daddy, l've missed you so much.
My dear, my dear,
don't cry, my baby.
''She was weak and desperate.
She was taking on sorrows
she had never known.
She tried, but she couldn't do it.
She couldn't end the baby's life.
Perhaps, giving birth
would be just the thing...
...to save herfrom this situation
she felt powerless over,...
...so the woman thought.
As the rain poured overher.''
Did you notice, did you see
how the garden has expanded?
l'll talk to the mayor and
get that wall demolished as well.
Then, this will be a huge place.
When you get married,
we can have the wedding here.
Since we will have a big garden.
My dear, my beautiful girl.
Only if yourmotherwas alive and
could have seen you all grown up...
She would have been dancing
at yourwedding with me.
She would take her grandchild
into herarms,...
...and shout at us like she used to.
She would say ''be quiet''.
l miss taking heron
when she was angry.
Dad, l'm pregnant.
Pregnant?
Dad, we were going to get married.
But please don't ask about it,
l can't tell you.
Yesterday, l went to get an abortion,
but l couldn't do it.
l feel it in my tummy, dad.
Dad.
''His daughter's baby and the facts
she could not speak of...
...were a bit too much
for a father...
...who was just trying to improve
his garden.
Neitherthis town, or his heart,
was a place able to understand it.''
The first kiss with you...
The first time being with you...
l always imagined doing these
things forthe first time with you.
There is someone else on your mind,
l know.
l heard she's a blonde girl.
But l'm yourwoman now, Hasmet.
Nupelda...
Will you be able to love me?
ls that necessary?
Dad?
Dad, won't you talk to me?
l need you to trust me, dad.
l can't tell you.
You are carrying the child of a man
who l don't even know.
You come home,
then say ''trust me''.
How can l face the people
in this town? You neverthink that.
When l go to yourmother's grave,
how do l explain this to her?
What do l tell that child?
How can l hold it?
You neverthink.
But you can stand before me and say
''trust me''.
Don't trust me, girl.
Don't trust me.
l will not take care of that child
in this house.
l will not call it my grandchild.
lf you want to give birth
to that child, do it elsewhere.
And from now on, don't call me ''dad''.
-Dad, come on, please.
-l said ''don't call me dad''!
Yourdaughter's got a bun
in the oven.
Where's the groom?
Won't he make an appearance?
He's a soldier, a soldier.
When he comes back from the army.
What should l do now, woman?
l can't discard it, l can't
put it off, l can't kick her out...
Should l kill myself,
should l kill her, what do l do?
You will forgive me, dad.
l am your daughter,
and this is yourgrandchild.
l broke your heart, l know.
But my heart is broken too.
l fell in love, dad! lt was not with
just some random guy!
Don't speak!
Don't tell me, tell yourmom!
Let's see if she will forgive you!
lf yourmotherwas alive now,...
...she would have caved your head in
with a stone!
Cave my head in then, dad.
You can do it too.
Go, girl, leave!
Donat make me kill my own child!
lf you will not forgive me,
then kill me!
l give you my blessing!
Eitherkill me orforgive me, dad!
Let God forgive you, my daughter.
l will not take that kid on my lap,
do you understand?
l will not take that kid on my lap!
Yagmur... Yagmur!
Yagmur!
-Dad!
My girl!
ls anybody there?
Hang on, girl, hang on.
Call a doctor, run, run!
Hold on, dear,
there is a doctorcoming, hold on.
Woman, what do l do now?
Kemal!
Unfortunately, these results are
negative too, Mrs. Nupelda.
But there are new techniques
developing every day.
There are a few more methods l would
like to offeras treatment for you.
lf you let me,
we can start a new treatment.
You are coming to the meeting.
Pick yourself up a little.
lt didn't work this time either.
But we'll try again
with anothermethod.
l want to give you a child so much.
''ln the mirror,
she only saw someone...
...who is trying to be a woman
with herdamaged femininity.
She felt incomplete.''
To get this hotel back will be
too tiring forus at the moment.
We have neitherthe personnel
northe time to deal with this thing.
We are here forsentimental reasons.
This hotel has been run by this
family for overtwenty years.
We know how valuable it is.
Think about my offer,
and get back to me.
Yes, Mr. Hasmet.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
This business will end here today.
That's what we are here for,
Mrs. Nupelda.
That's exactly
what we are doing.
No. Yourgoal is to take advantage
of ourweaknesses,...
...and sell off the hotel to us
at an exorbitant price.
lf you were sitting
in front of my uncle,...
...he would have ripped yourtongue
out of yourhead.
l miss you so much.
Hasmet!
lf you evertry to undermine
my authority again, l'll kill you.
You are the one letting them
undermine yourauthority.
You let them spit
on ourfamily values.
lt was a bluff. They will
get back to us within two days.
They can't sell it to anyone but us,
and you know it.
Do you know why
we can't have kids?
Because you can't get that bimbo
out of yourmind.
Show them the masculinity
you are not showing me,...
...so that we can get back
what this family has lost.
Don't make me.
l know, you will love it.
You saw nothing but this
while growing up.
But don't force me to do it.
No more of this.
No more of this!
Sir, your phone...
''Alpago: l Found Her''
Yagmur, there's someone here,
asking for you.
Why didn't you listen to me?
l've been looking for you
formonths.
Zeynep, don't leave, you can stay.
There was nothing to listen to.
You were going t get married.
What should l have done,
become your mistress?
l don't know why you are here.
But you'd bettergo.
My husband will retum soon.
Yagmur?. Yagmur!
Okay, calm down.
How's it going?
l can't talk right now.
l see, you still haven't finished it.
Don't let me disturb you.
Don't forget about
the engagement rehearsal tomorrow.
Alright.
l'll call you.
''Hasmet was watching
the lives of the people...
...that were built
on his unhappiness.
He stopped questioning.
He just watched.''
Brother, come on. These monsters
finished all the meat.
Come on, come here.
Alpago.
-Yes, sir?
Wow, brother...
Can you believe that Turhan
has a child, and we got to see it?
How time flies, doesn't it?
lt would have been nice
to see your kid...
-What happened to youreye?
-My eye?
ls it Hamza?
Oh, brother...
Where's Nupe?
Why isn't she coming down?
She has the flu,
she's not coming down...
...because she doesn't want to
infect the children.
They are bringing their children here
on purpose.
Trying to send me a message.
l'm suffering more than you are.
Some nights,
you kiss me in a way that...
l know it's not me on your mind
at that moment.
You kiss that bimbo.
-Nupe...
Look, Hasmet, l will let you
think about hertonight.
Come on, let's do it.
You don't love me, l know.
Think of the woman that you do love.
Let me give you a child, please.
Please?
Don't run away!
What is this obsession you have?
Why can't you save yourself?
Give it to me.
Nupe, give it to me.
''She could not reach
the man she loved.
The walls that needed to be taken
down were too tiring for Nupelda.
As Hasmet tried to live the life
that was imposed on him,...
...he could not escape his fate.
Aword, a sound, or a song would
take him back to her. Every time...''
''Pain...
He felt the pain down to his
bones. The fire would not go out.
Time is medicine, but
could it extinguishing this flame?''
Run, get overhere.
Come here, come here.
Look, why am l here, do you know?
l'm going to lstanbul.
l will participate in a conference
forthree days.
l would like for you to come too.
-No, l can't leave my father.
Uncle Huseyin, would you like me to
take you to lstanbul?
Yes! Yes! Yes!
-What are you doing?
-l'm asking yourfather.
You guys go, lstanbul
may prove to be too much forme.
-Mom, please.
-Say ''yes''.
You guys should go for a few days
and let me enjoy my privacy.
Please, mom, please.
Okay, okay. You think
l'm going to break yourheart?
High five.
Come on, hurry.
Kemal, stop it.
Be nice.
Give me yourhand.
When you get back,
l will have a surprise for you.
Stop, l want to play.
Here you go.
Stop.
l'm sorry.
Come on.
You lied to me.
You are not married.
Yourlast names are different.
You are staying in separate rooms.
-How did you find us?
-l didn't find you, you found me.
Yagmur, is that my son?
Kemal, please let me go.
We will leave, l promise.
Yagmur, is that ourson?
Don't make me suffer any more,
please.
For years now,
l'm living like l've died.
Please don't disappear again.
Go to your room and wait forme.
Be alone.
Wait for me in yourroom, please.
-Kemal, let me go.
l'll find you.
l'll find you, Yagmur,
don't run from me.
l beg of you,
go to yourroom and wait for me.
You can stay down here,
l'lljoin you shortly.
No, l'm fine, l'm fine.
l just need a little time alone.
Okay, talk to you later, Sinan.
Every breath l took after you,
was not like breathing.
l lost all of my soul along with you.
l've never loved any otherwoman
but you, Yagmur.
ls he ourson?
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why have you dragged me
through hell for all these years?
They told me not to say anything.
-Who?
-Hamza and yourbrother.
They tried to get me
to have an abortion.
Hamza said ''have this child,
and we are all going to die''.
They said they would kill you
if l didn't stay away.
l was afraid of
something happening to you.
All of them
will have to answerto me.
lt wasn't easy to raise him.
l always lived on the edge.
Afraid that somebody would try to
take my child away from me.
l want forhim...
...to have a different kind of world
than the world you have.
Please, let us go.
That's not possible.
lt's no longer possible.
Mom, where are you?
Mom, can we go to the pool
with Uncle Sinan?
-ls yourname Kemal?
-Yes.
My name is Kemal too.
Nice to meet you.
Kemal, come on,
are we ready for a swim...
Mr. Sinan, our doctor.
We came to lstanbul with him,
he had a conference.
Mr. Kemal is...
...a friend of the family.
-Nice to meet you.
-Likewise.
-Do you like lstanbul?
-Yes, l liked it a lot.
You know, l'm staying
at a hotel forthe first time.
lt has a huge pool.
Mom, can we go?
-Of course, my love.
lt was nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Kemal, come on,
let's go down to the pool.
You did a great job raising him.
Without him, l couldn't have
gone on with anything.
Every day without you was like hell.
His presence has lessened my pain.
l promise you, from now on,
it's you, me, and ourson.
l don't care about the rest.
-But you are married...
-You two are my family.
Please don't disappear again.
Give me a chance to fix everything.
You grew within me from day to day.
So, this was the reason.
l felt it.
You haven't forgotten me.
ls it possible to forget you?
We have a son who has youreyes.
Today, l will send you to a place.
No one knows it but me.
l will take care of everything, and
a few days later, l willjoin you.
l don't want you to
endanger yourself, Kemal.
He has grown accustomed
to being fatherless.
Please don't take this away from me.
l have a right to it.
l grew up without a father.
Give me a chance to raise him
the way l was neverraised.
Please.
What's up, you've called 50 times
since this moming.
l hope there's nothing wrong.
l'm at the hotel.
Be here in an hour.
Mom, l'm sleepy.
Alright, my love,
you can sleep on the way now.
Come here, you, come here!
What did you do?
-What are you saying?
You moron!
Didn't you say she had a miscarriage?
Wasn't she supposed to
nevertum up again?
That's what she told me.
-Should l kill you now, God damn...
-Hamza!
Have you gotten big enough to be able
to come to our home and harass us?
Yourson bumed us.
Yourstep-son is digging the graves
for both Turhan and himself.
Mom, the girl said
''l will stay away from your brother''.
She's there!
She gave birth to the kid.
l saw them with my own eyes!
Do you realize what sort of a fire
you have cast us all into?
He will take woman and the kid
and disappear.
Lady Fadile, whateverhappens
afterthat, will happen to us!
l give up.
Hamza?
Get yourthings packed.
l don't understand.
l'll pick you up in an hour.
Transferall the bank accounts
within an hour.
Come to where l tell you to come
when l call.
Are we really going finally?
We are going halfway around the
world, away from all this crap.
l'll call you.
What are you doing here?
Hamza, where are you going?
l'm not the dog of this house
Hamza.
l'm yourwife!
l said, ''where are you going''!
You haven't been around
forseveral days already.
You are running away with that
bankerwoman, aren't you?
Get off my back!
Call the hospital!
She has a broken neck
and is in serious condition.
We are trying to keep her alive,
but herlife will neverbe the same.
l had to do it,
or l would have lost all of you.
You spared yourown son,
but tried to kill mine.
-Brother!
-Turhan.
-Brother, forgive me!
-Shut up, boy.
Brother!
So, l'm the guilty one, huh?
There are thousands of men...
...who are eaming theirbread money
due to this marriage.
Now these people will cry out
forblood. Starting with Sitki!
l didn't shoot Mr. lhsan.
l'm not going down for it.
You didn't come with me,
you weren't there.
You don't know what happened.
-l told you not to go!
Whatever happened, happened, Hasmet.
We grew up like brothers, you and l.
l've always tried to protect you, but
you know this world as well as l do.
They will not forget about blood.
There is no escape from this.
lf you hadn't shot that man,
l'd already be long gone!
l stayed to protect you.
The bank called.
You tried to empty youraccounts.
You didn't go because
business was slow.
You didn't have any money
to take with you.
You were going to profit
from this marriage too.
You waited.
Hamza, you tried to kill my son.
You left my sisterfor dead.
You know that
you can't escape this.
They won't let you live.
l know.
-l was very worried about you.
-Here l am.
Look at what ourguys brought me
from the security room.
Sitki, are you sure?
ls it her?
l'm sure, my sister, l'm sure.
l also looked at the hotel records.
Her name is Yagmur.
This is the girl.
Today is my day.
Shall l use my voice now?
Do l have yourpermission?
lt's like everything's fine,
like...
...l've gone on vacation to a summer
house with you and our child.
l wish that were true.
l could neverlive my own life.
For me, the realest moment
is this moment.
Alpago.
-Yes, sir?
-Prepare the barbecue.
-Sure.
What will happen now?
l have to go.
You will wait for me here.
lf l don't come back
until tomorrow night,...
...the guys will take you from here.
Don't go.
We can go
to another part of the world.
Aplace they can't find us...
We can establish new lives.
Please, Kemal,
l can't bearto lose you again.
Please.
Sir.
God loves the patient ones.
Of course, my heart is good.
That day will come, l said
to myself, l've been patient.
God has granted me
a part of my prayers, Hasmet.
Look, if you noticed,
l said ''part of my prayers''.
Because l have Turhan at gunpoint.
lf it were you instead,
then it would be complete.
-Alpago, get the car.
-Of course.
Kemal, l beg of you, don't go.
Please, please.
l have to go.
lf you want me to
come back to you as Kemal,...
...l have to leave Hasmet with them.
You are the only woman
l've everloved.
Don't you everforget that.
Don't go.
-Alpago, take Turhan away.
-No.
Keep your anger inside.
Don't do anything crazy.
Alpago, there is no end to this.
Come on, take Turhan
and get out of here.
-Allow me, let me kill them all.
-Come on, come on.
There is no end to it.
Come on, champ.
Take Turhan and get out of here,
come on.
Let them go.
Let us speak alone.
-Sitki, leave us alone.
-Sister!
Sitki, get out!
lt didn't have to be this way.
l'd have given anything for you.
l tried so hard.
But you broke the agreement
between us, Hasmet.
You made a toy out of my dignity.
You played
with my sense of femininity.
You humiliated me
towards my family.
l have a son with her.
He is a part of me.
Alright.
l accept.
Bring the child,...
...but leave that bimbo
out of our lives.
Set out a new life for yourself.
l have worked very hard
to cool this fire.
Like you, l have sacrificed myself.
But it didn't work,
the flames didn't die out.
Don't go.
For God's sake, don't go.
lf you stay with me,
l'll protect you.
No one can hurt you
while you're by my side.
lf l leave here,
they will shoot me, right?
Yes.
Well, if l die,
does that stop the bloodshed?
Don't do it, Hasmet.
Nupelda, if l die,
will this warstop?
-Put down the gun.
-Nupe, will the blood feud stop?
Sister!
No more talking, shoot him!
That is ourfather's killer,
standing in front of you!
lf you don't shoot, l'm going to!
-l said ''leave us alone'', Sitki!
He's trying to deceive you!
He's trying to trick you!
l will not be able to rest
until l have bled this bastard out!
l beg you, stay with me.
l beg you.
Come on, sister, shoot!
l neverknew that this pain
would cause you to stray...
...and rob me of my heart.
ls this the ring?
Yes.
l neverknew that this pain,
Would cause you to stray,
And rob me of my heart.
l never knew that l had
Rains and blood inside.
l never knew that
What l had the most,
Would have to settle for
What l don't have.
That the farthest
Would become the closest,
And that the closest
Would then be lost to me.
l never knew.
Are you mad at me,
My one and only?
lf you are, it's been too long,
Just so you know.
Bumt-scented
winds hit my face.
My shivering is
Keeping me from breathing.
Hesitant words are
Stuck in my throat.
They took the nearest right tum
And parked themselves.
They were disobedient words.
They say loving is a secret by name.
Noisy letters are
becoming silent.
They are leaving Their
most intimate feelings behind.
Are you not tired of my voice,
My silent scream?
Your place is within my mess.
Let's tum it into a dream.
SouthFreak.Com